

Karthik Chitturi

) +91 9398954816

Github_Profile





SUMMARY

I am a motivated & self-learning student having experience of one year as Full-Stack Web Developer.My objective is to obtain a challenging position that will help me learn & explore more technologies and utilize them in solving real world problems.

EDUCATIONAL DETAILS

SRKREC,Bhimavaram	2021-25
Bachelors of Technology in CSD	8.12/10
Aditya Junior College	2019-21
Intermediate Education	9.4/10
Aditya Public School	2019
Secondary Education	10/10

WORK EXPERIENCE

MCR Web Solutions **Project Intern**

Under Dr.M.Suresh Babu

May 2021 - Present

- · Presently working as a Jr.Software Developer under the guidance of our mentor.
- · Building user-friendly and responsive websites for clients
- Some of the projects built as a SDE during the internship Kshatriya Kalyanlu Website for UoH SRKR Alumni Website and many more projects!

Bhimavaram Online Project Intern May 2021 - Present Under Dr.M.Suresh Babu

- Digital Content Creation Creating posts and videos for the stores in the app
- Social Media Marketing Promoting the stroes through Instagram and FaceBook.
- Online Housie & Quiz- Managing and conducting the Online Housie Game and Real-time Quiz every weekend and on festivals Online Housie Online Quiz

FalconX Project Intern April 30 - Present Under Dr.A.Naveen

 Part of the team that is currently working on frontend and user experience aspects of a upcoming banking application.

PROJECTS

Kshatriya Kalyanlu

A user-friendly & responsieve website created for a matrimonial office using basic web technologies and Bootstarp framework.

Ctfppb2023

A user-friendly & responsieve website that is solely designed for School of Life Sciences, University of Hyderabad. The website is about an yearly international conference on biological topics. The site is built using basic web technologies, Bootstrap and Tailwind CSS.

The SAANA

SAANA -> SRKREC Alumni Association of North America . as the name tells that the project is about connecting the alumni and managaing all the data of the passed out students through a good looking website

E-Commerce Site

This is an E-commerce site for a sweet shop named Sri Ramana HomeFoods.The E-com site is designed and customized as per the client requests. It includes custom whatsapp order management and direct whatsapp communication.

And there are many more porjects that I have done while exploring other parts of the Web Technologies.All of them are hosted in my Github account.

HACKTHONS & TRAININGS

TECHEDEN 2.0

VIT Amaravathi

Participated as a team of 5 members in the 24hr hackthon and developed a platform that connects working professional and learners to gain industry ready skills

STARTUP EXPO

NITAP Tadepalliqudem

Presented the idea of establishing a revenue generating start up using the our own built softwares i.e., Housie, Quiz and Spell Bee.

5 DAY BOOTCAMP ON DATA SCIENCE SRKREC **USING PYTHON**

Attended 5 Day Bootcamp on Data Science using Python and learned about tools like Spyder, Numpy, Pandas etc.

SRKREC Bhimavaram

Developed a web application that tracks student's progress and learning outcomes in real-time.

SKILLS

DATABASES

PROGRAMMING

C,Python,JavaScript,PHP

Git, Visual Studio Code, Android **DEVELOPER TOOLS** Studio, GitHub, PyCharm

MySQL, Mongo DB

WEB DEVELOPMENT FRMAEWORKS/LIBRARIES

Html,Css,Basic JavaScript Node Js,ReactJs, Bootstrap,

Tailwind CSS

TOOLS FAMILIAR WITH

Postman, Blender, Unity 3D,

BuildBox